다들 어디 갔어요?
Hey, where is everybody?
The 2:30 jaywalk run-through. Yeah, but it's not 2:30 yet.
2시 30분 회의
진행중이에요
아직 2시 반
안 됐는데요
That's 'cause they moved it to 2:00. They sent a memo.
2시로 변경 됐거든요
메모 남겼었어요
Alrught, I need an update on Budapest. Sorry I'm late for-
부다페스트 쪽
정보가 필요해
늦어서 죄송해요
- Surprise! - Hey, surprise!
놀랐죠!
생일 축하해요!
Happy Birthday!
That is totally unexpected.
전혀 예상도 못했어요
I'm at a complete loss for what to say
뭐라고 해야 할지
모르겠어요
except that it's not my birthday.
오늘은 제 생일이
아니란 말 빼고요
But it will be in about six days.
엿새 있으면
생일이긴 하죠
How about we not quibble over details
사소한 차이엔
집착하지 말고
- and you make a wish? - I can't blow out the candle,
- 소원을 빌지 그래요
- 그게...
진짜 생일 아니면
촛불 끄지 않아요
not if it's not my actual birthday, 'cause it's bad luck.
악운이 낀다고 믿거든요
Does this mean no cake? Yes, cake. Have at it.
그럼 케이크도 안 돼요?
안될 거 없지
어서들 들어
There you go again, lighting up a room.
또 그러는군요
분위기 착 가라앉혀요
So the sudden craving for chai...
갑자기 차가
마시고 싶으셨다?
- Subterfuge. - Auggie, you are six whole days off.
- 구실이었죠
- 오기, 엿새나 이르잖아요
You don't need subterfuge. You need a calendar.
당신에게 필요한 건
구실이 아니라 달력이었어요
Unless... you know some reason why
아니면...
다음 주엔 내가 여기 없을
이유를 알고 있는 거겠죠
I won't be here next week to celebrate.
Annie.
애니
A word in my office when you're done here.
여기 일 끝내면
내 사무실로 와
Auggie...
오기?
절 파리로 보내신다고요?
You're sending me to Paris?
See? Now I'm already having second thoughts.
봤지? 벌써 재고하게 되네
But you just gave me the assignment.
하지만 임무를
맡기셨잖아요
Yeah. But you've got that look.
그랬지, 하지만
그 표정이 문제야
표정이요?
무슨 표정이요?
Look? What look?
여성 요원을 처음으로
파리에 보낼 때마다
The look that every female operative gets the first time I send her to Paris.
내가 보게 되는 표정이지
Your pupils are dilating. Did you even hear what your mission was?
동공이 확대됐잖아
임무가 뭔지
제대로 듣긴 했어?
물론이죠, 파리에서
정보원을 만드는 일이죠
Yes! To cultivate an asset in Paris.
Her name is Salma Devrient.
이름은 샐마 데브리언트고
클리시 수 부아에서
태어나고 자랐죠
She was born and raised in Clichy-Sous-Bois.
Her father is French. Her mother is from Aleppo.
아버지는 프랑스인이고
어머니는 알레포 출신이에요
She works for the Syrian embassy as the social secretary.
시리아 대사관에서
사교 담당 비서로 일하고요
And we think she might be vulnerable why?
정보원이 될 수 있을 거라
생각하는 이유는?
Because her fiance of the past two years just broke up with her,
2년간 사귀었던 약혼자와
얼마 전 파혼했으니까요
and she is a week late in her rent.
집세도 일주일이나
밀리고 있고요
Joan, look. My pupils are fine.
조안, 보세요
제 동공은 문제없어요
Okay.
좋아
Do we think that the Syrians might be reconstituting their weapons program?
시리아에서 무기 개발 계획을
재개하고 있다고 보는 건가요?
대사관 내에 협력자가 있으면
좋겠다고 생각하는 거야
We think it would be helpful to have a friend inside the embassy, nothing more.
다른 건 없어
It's hard to believe there isn't someone
파리 지부에
이 일을 맡을 만한
in the Paris station who's in a better position to do that.
더 나은 사람이 없다니
믿기질 않는데요
Are you gonna make me have third thoughts?
다른 사람을
고려해볼까?
이런 임무를 맡고 싶어하는
요원들은 많아
'Cause there's plenty of people who want to take this mission.
No. Thank you. I appreciate the opportunity.
아니에요
기회를 주셔서 감사해요
You've done some solid work here, Annie, but at the end of the day,
넌 여기서의 일도
괜찮게 해냈지만
결국엔 정보원을
양성하는 일이
it's the cultivation of intelligence assets
that determines how successful you are in the CIA.
CIA에서 네 성공을
결정하는 거야
- Assets like Salma. - I understand.
- 샐마 같은 정보원 말이야
- 알겠습니다
Just go and use your best judgment.
가서 잘 판단해서 행동해
And bring back receipts.
영수증은 꼭 챙기고
파리
= 프랑스 =
♬ Anywhere you looked ♬
Au Revoir Simone
So you've been there three days already.
거기 간지도
벌써 사흘째예요
뭘 알아냈나요?
What have you learned?
I've learned she likes her routines.
똑같은 일상을
보내는 걸 좋아하고
She's got a good eye for accessories.
액세서리 취향이
훌륭하다는 걸 알아냈어요
And that she's not so crazy about her coworkers.
직장 동료들과 그다지
친하지 않다는 것도요
결국엔 샐마와 접촉하는 일에
착수해야 할 거예요
You know, you are eventually going to have to initiate contact with her.
이번 일은 쓸데없는 일이
아니라고요
This isn't a total boondoggle.
Is that your way of telling me you miss me? Yeah, sure, joke now.
내가 보고싶단 말을
그렇게 표현하는 거예요?
지금이야 농담하지만
Wait till the bean counters get their hands on you.
회계부에서 당신한테
벼르고 있을 거예요
Don't expect those excuses to hold water with accounting.
그런 변명들이 회계부에
통할 거라 기대하지 말아요
Or Joan, for that matter.
그 점에 대해서라면
조안도 마찬가지예요
Stay focused, find your in, and all will be fine.
집중해서 틈을 찾아봐요
다 잘 풀릴 거예요
I think... I have an opening.
아무래도 틈을
찾아낸 거 같아요
19th century portraits. You call that an opening?
19세기 초상화
전시회예요
그런 걸 틈이라고 불러요?
대화를 시작할
더 좋은 방법 있어요?
Got any good conversation starters?
Yeah, I do, actually, but they all require that you not be able to see.
그럼요
물론 있죠
하지만 당신이 맹인일 때만
통하는 방법이에요
Thanks.
됐어요
-==팎읔襟있蹈허헙룽窘==-
굶俚캥쏭묩欺構슥직, 拮쐐痰黨庚둡촐
영자막
www.addic7ed.com
Season 2 Episode 2
Good Advices
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
줅소큽景묏 뒤랗센뒤2섞
-=팎읔襟俚캥莉=-
럇陋：
叫뚤：
珂쇌菉：kami
한글번역 에렝아이
디시인사이드 기미갤
CIA HEADQUARTERS LANGLEY, VIRGINIA
CIA 본부
= 랭리, 버지니아 주=
Did you ask for a postponement?
연기해달라고
해봤어요?
연기하고 싶지 않아
I don't want a postponement.
You know, I can do that thing with the guy with the strings getting pulled.
제가 손 써볼 수 있어요
연줄이 좀 있어요
전화 한 통이면 돼요
- One phone call. - It's my civic duty.
내 시민으로서의 의무야
Okay. But what if you get stuck on some OJ-like trial?
OJ심슨 재판 같은 데
걸리면 어떡해요?
You could be sequestered for weeks.
몇 주씩이나
갇혀 있을 거예요
I'm not gonna be sequestered, because I won't even be selected.
갇혀 있지 않을 거야
배심원으로 선출되지
않을 테니까
You don't know that.
그건 모르는 거죠
If you were on trial, would you want me on your jury?
자기가 재판을 받는다면
내가 배심원이었으면 좋겠어?
Can I take the fifth on that one?
묵비권을 사용해도 되나요?
I'll put everything together you'll need before I leave.
떠나기 전에 필요한 건
전부 준비해둘게
Do we have a status on Annie?
애니 상황은 어때?
She's making some real progress.
큰 진전을 보이고 있어요
그럼 아직
접촉하지 않았다는 거네?
So she hasn't established contact.
- She's getting super-close. - Let's read her in
굉장히 가까워지고 있어요
다마스쿠스의 소문을
애니에게 알려줘
on the chatter out of Damascus, okay?
Maybe accelerate things over there. I'll get right on it.
좀 더 일을
서두를지도 모르지
바로 할게요
I wouldn't feel comfortable reporting for jury duty
자기를 신뢰하지 않았으면
이렇게 일을 맡기고
if I didn't trust you to fill in, Auggie.
배심원 소환에 응하는 일이
편하지 않았을 거야
You're gonna do fine without me.
나 없이도
자긴 잘 해낼거야
Okay.
알았어요
I'M SORRY
죄송합니다만
이 카드는 지불이 거절되네요
YOUR CARD'S BEEN DECLINED.
SHOULD WE TRY ANOTHER?
다른 카드는 없으세요?
NO, THANK YOU.
아뇨, 됐어요
왜 가게에서 바로
접촉하지 않았어요?
Why didn't you just run her down right there in the store?
Because, Auggie, it would have embarrassed her, confronting her in public like that.
사람들 많은 장소에선
샐마가 당혹스러워했을 거예요
I assume you staged the dummy bag.
가짜 가방은 잘 준비해뒀죠?
Yeah. Tour guide, Metro map, key to my hotel room.
네, 여행 가이드나
지하철 지도
호텔방 열쇠를 뒀어요
Smithsonian business cards.
스미소니언 직원증도요
Hey, guys, run a number for me.
번호 검색 좀 해줄래요?
43-59-14-17.
43-59-14-17 이에요
See if anything turns up.
- 뭐가 나오는지 봐줘요
- 연락이 올 거라 확신해요?
You sure she's gonna call you back?
Maybe she'll like her new bag better.
새 가방을 더
좋아할 수도 있잖아요
If worse comes to worse, I'll call her later,
만일의 경우엔
내가 연락해야겠지만
but I want Salma to be the one who reaches out.
샐마 쪽에서
접근했으면 좋겠어요
It's better if she feels responsible.
샐마 쪽이 책임감을
느끼는 게 더 나아요
And what did it cost to lay this freudian trap of yours?
프로이드식 함정을 파는데
들어간 비용은요?
6, 000. Six-
6000이요
약 900만원
육...
6, 000 Euros for a pocketbook?
핸드백 하나에
6천 유로요?
Six grand's not bad. Full retail's closer to seven.
6천이면 괜찮네
소매가는 7천에 가까워
Can you return it when you're done
일 마치고
환불할 순 있어요?
or convert it into a condo?
아니면 콘도로
바꾸는 건 어때요?
You're obviously not a woman.
당신은 확실히
여자가 아니군요
Joan will understand the underlying psychology.
조안이라면 기저의 심리를
이해해줄 거예요
No. Joan would not understand.
아니
조안도 이해하지
못할 거야
Oh. Hey, Joan.
안녕하세요, 조안
Auggie, little heads up next time.
오기, 다음 번엔
경고 좀 해줄래요?
내가 몰래 접근하기 힘든
남자가 아니라서 말이죠
Hey, it's not like I'm the most difficult guy to sneak up on.
Annie, you do realize we didn't send you to Paris to scout fashion week.
애니, 패션위크 염탐하라고
파리 보낸 게 아닌 건 알지?
Did you read her in yet?
아직 얘기 안 해줬어?
Read me in on what? There's been increased chatter out of Damascus.
무슨 일 말씀이세요?
다마스쿠스에서
들리는 소문이 있어요
마흐무드 카나안이
이동 중인 것 같아요
We think Mahmoud Kanaan is on the move.
Chemical Kanaan's here? In Paris?
화학자 카나안이 여기예요?
파리에?
We don't know. It'd be nice if you could stop shopping and help us answer that question.
우리도 몰라
네가 쇼핑 그만 두고
그 질문의 답을 찾는 일을
도와줬으면 좋겠어
Okay. Can I get something to I.D. him with, a photo...
알았어요, 그를 알아볼
방법이 없을까요?
- 사진이나...
- 그러고 싶지만 불가능해요
We would if we could, but we can't. Chemical Kanaan is a ghost.
화학자 카나안은
유령이에요
20 years flouting IAEA nonproliferation sanctions,
20년 동안 IAEA의
핵확산방지조약을 어겨왔지만
and we still don't know what he looks like.
여전히 생김새도 몰라요
Hold on. That's my other line.
잠시만요
전화가 왔어요
Okay. I don't like to use this term, but...
좋아, 이런 말하긴 싫지만
If it helps keep anyone in line while I'm out of pocket,
내가 자릴 비운 동안
일 처리에 도움이 된다면
you can say you're in charge.
자기가 책임자라고
말해도 돼
What-he's in charge? Like I said.
오기가 책임자라고요?
말했듯이
I promise not to abuse you.
자넬 혹사시키지
않겠다고 약속하지
애니 워커 씨인가요?
ARE YOU ANNIE WALKER?
YES.
네
당신이 샐마 드브리언트예요?
YOU ARE SALMA DEVRIENT?
데브리언트예요
영어로 말씀하셔도 돼요
Devrient. It's okay if you like to speak in English.
Merci-I mean, thank you. I'm so sorry for the mix-up.
메르씨...
아니, 고마워요
잘못 가져가서
정말 죄송해요
아무것도 건드리지 않았어요
I didn't touch anything inside.
아뇨, 죄송할 거 없어요
저도 건드리지 않았어요
No. Of course not. Neither did I.
Couldn't help but wonder, though, what you paid for it.
다만 얼마에 사셨을까
궁금하긴 했어요
Just feel like an idiot who still pays full retail.
제가 정가 다 내고 사는
바보라는 생각이 들어서요
I don't remember.
기억나질 않네요
Oh. Look at me being so rude.
너무 무례하게
군 것 같네요
당신이...
누군지도 모르는데
I don't even know you yet.
벌써부터 사적인
질문을 드리고 있네요
I'm already asking personal questions.
- Won't you please sit down? - I really should be going.
- 잠깐 앉아계실래요?
- 지금 가봐야 해요
Oh, please? I ordered this whole bottle of wine by mistake.
부탁해요, 실수로
와인을 병째 주문했어요
Verre... Bouteille. I get so confused.
잔... 병...
너무 헷갈려서요
You have to help me finish it.
같이 마셔줘요
I bought the bag after my fiance left. I couldn't afford it, really.
약혼자가 떠난 뒤로
산 가방이에요
형편에 걸맞지 않은
씀씀이였죠
But it makes you feel better.
그래도 기분은
좋아졌잖아요
We call that retail therapy in the States.
미국에선 그걸
"쇼핑 치료"라고 부르죠
쇼핑 치료요?
네, 마음에 드네요
Retail therapy? Yes. I like that.
It works much better than ice cream.
아이스크림보단
효과가 확실해요
적어도 카드가
거절당하기 전까지는요
At least until your credit runs out.
Yeah. You need a better-paying job. Yeah. A better breed of fiance.
맞아요, 더 좋은
일자리가 필요하죠
네, 더 나은
약혼자를 구해야죠
Sometimes the two come hand-in-hand.
가끔은 양손에 한 명씩
쥐고 있어도 돼요
I really should be going.
이제 정말 가봐야겠어요
They embassy will want me to report my bag being missing.
가방 잃어버린 것 때문에
대사관에 보고해야 해요
별 탈 없이
되찾았잖아요?
Oh, but you got it all back in one piece.
알아요, 하지만
규정이 그래요
I know, but they have their rules.
They will want me to change all the locks and passwords.
자물쇠나 비밀번호도
늘 바꾸라고 하죠
I know this is really last-minute,
이건 정말
마지막 부탁인데
but I have to go to this black tie event tonight.
오늘 밤 제가 정장 차림
행사를 가야 하거든요
I don't want to go by myself. It will be so boring.
혼자 가기 싫어요
너무 지루할 것 같아요
You want to go with me? Tonight?
저보고 같이 가자고요?
오늘 밤에요?
Do you already have plans? Uh, no.
다른 계획 있어요?
아뇨
I don't know. I-
글쎄요, 제가...
I kind of met this man yesterday.
어제 남자를 만났는데
You little minx. You work so fast.
이런 능글맞은 아가씨를 봤나
벌써 손을 써뒀군요
What's his name? Where'd you meet him?
이름은 뭐예요?
어디서 만났어요?
His name is George. But it's nothing, really.
이름은 조지예요
하지만 그게 다예요
아직 아무런
사이도 아니에요
Not yet anyway. But he said he was going to call.
그래도 전화해 준다고
했거든요
So you're gonna go home and wait by the phone?
그럼 집에서
전화 기다리려고요?
Take it from me-
제 말 명심해요
you gotta play harder to get.
좀 더 비싸게 굴어야죠
Do you go to party like this for work every night?
매일 밤마다 일 때문에
이런 파티에 오는 건가요?
Not every night.
매일 밤은 아니에요
Oh, I need to find the ladies' room. Oh. Okay. I'll meet you right over there.
잠깐 화장실에
들러야겠어요
그래요, 저쪽에서 만나요
Okay.
알았어요
TWO CHAMPAGNE COCKTAILS, PLEASE.
샴페인 칵테일
두 잔 부탁해요
THAT'S A GORGEOUS DRESS.
멋진 드레스네요
THANK YOU.
고마워요
제 침실에서
더욱 멋져 보일 거 같은데요
IT WOULD LOOK BETTER ON MY BEDROOM FLOOR.
NOT IN THIS LIFETIME.
이번 생애에선
없을 일이에요
운명을 믿지 않는
모양이군요?
And you didn't believe in kismet?
Listen, buddy, if you-
이봐요, 당신...
Bon soir. Bon soir.
안녕하세요
Uh, this is, uh... A pleasant surprise, I hope.
- 아... 이건
- 뜻밖의 기쁨이면 좋겠네요
맞아요
정말이요
It is. Very much so.
Who knew you were a patron of the arts?
당신이 미술 후원자일 줄은
몰랐는데요?
Well, what can I say?
달리 드릴 말씀이 없군요
I like beautiful things.
나는 아름다운 것들을
좋아하니까요
That tux does suit you.
턱시도 잘 어울리네요
I'm contractually obligated to wear it every time I'm in Paris.
계약상 파리에 올 때마다
입을 의무가 있는 거예요
It's good for the image... of the city. You seem distracted.
이 도시의 이미지에
잘 어울리죠
뭔가 정신없어 보이네요
내가 방해라도 되고 있나요?
Am I keeping you from anything?
You are, actually.
사실 맞아요
You don't mind if we reschedule this little reunion, do you?
다른 때 재회의 시간을
가져도 괜찮겠죠?
Enough said. I have business to attend to myself. Thank you, Eyal.
괜찮아요, 나도
내 할 일이 있으니까요
고마워요, 에이얼
일종의 예의라고
생각합시다
Let's consider it a courtesy-
전문가로서
서로에 대한 예의로요
one professional to the other.
By the way, that switch you did with the bag...
그건 그렇고 가방을
바꿔치기한 건...
Excellent spycraft there. Well played.
훌륭한 스파이
기술이었어요
잘 했어요
And much more fashionable
취리히에서 티타늄 가방
옮겼던 거에 비해
than that titanium thing you lugged around Zurich.
훨씬 세련됐어요
- How do you know- - George?
- 그걸 어떻게?
- 조지?
당신에게선 놀라움이
끊이질 않네요
YOU ARE A CONSTANT SOURCE OF SURPRISE.
나의 작은 벌새
MY LITTLE HUMMINGBIRD.
You two know each other?
아는 사이예요?
Remember that man I told you about?
제가 말했던 남자 있죠?
만났다던 남자요
이 사람이에요
The one I just met. This is him.
Pleasure to meet you. The pleasure's all mine, George.
만나서 반갑습니다
제가 반갑죠, 조지
Thank you so much for bringing me with you.
절 데리고 와줘서
정말 고마워요
신데렐라가 된 기분이에요
I feel like Cinderella.
Perfect timing.
완벽한 타이밍이군
Thank you so much.
정말 고맙습니다
Shall we?
가실까요?
환상적이죠?
세상이 이렇게 좁다니
It's surreal, isn't it? How small is the world.
And you two have so much in common.
두 사람 공통점도 많아요
- Really? - George exports antiquities out of Cyprus,
그래요?
조지는 키프로스 골동품을
수출하는 일을 하고
and Annie represents the Smithsonian institute.
애니는 스미소니언
협회에서 일하잖아요
나중에 얘기라고
한번 나눠야겠네요
Perhaps we should, uh, talk later.
Oh, we should definitely talk later.
물론이죠, 꼭 한번
이야기 나눠야죠
How exactly did you two meet?
두 분 어떻게
만나셨다고요?
That's a funny story, because he was here in the museum.
재밌는 얘기가 있어요
여기 박물관에서
만났거든요
- Just yesterday. - Right here?
바로 어제요
여기서요?
No... it was actually, uh, 19th century portraits.
아뇨, 실은 19세기
초상화 전시회였죠
Yes. I was by myself after work,
맞아요
일 끝나고
혼자 들렀는데
and from out of nowhere, George came in
갑자기 조지가 나타나서
asking me how I felt about the brush strokes.
붓놀림에 대한 감상이
어떠냐고 물었죠
And before I knew it,
그리곤 그걸
깨닫기도 전에
we were spending the next nine hours together.
아홉 시간이나 함께
시간을 보내게 됐죠
It's kismet.
운명이네요
조지도 똑같은 말을 했어요
That's exactly what George said!
Did you hear that, George?
방금 들었어요, 조지?
I feel like dancing. Would you care to dance?
춤추고 싶은 기분이 드네요
함께 추실까요?
좋죠
I would love to. Will you be okay on your own, Annie?
혼자 있어도 되겠어요, 애니?
Oh, of course.
물론이죠
Don't worry about me!
제 걱정은 하지 마요
Hey, what's up? We have a little problem.
네, 무슨 일이에요?
문제가 조금 생겼어요
Your kid's home sick from school, you've got a big Powerpoint presentation to make,
아이가 아프다고
연락이 올 수도 있고
중요한 프레젠테이션이
있을 수도 있고
your boss is on your ass.
당신 목을 죄는 상관이
있을 수도 있어요
If any of you find any of those excuses on the tips of your tongues,
누구라도 그런 변명이
목구멍까지 올라왔다면
please leave them there.
다시 삼키시길
부탁드립니다
I've heard them all before.
다 들어본 얘기입니다
In a moment, we will begin Voir dire,
이제 곧 예비 심문
선서를 시작합니다
which is the process by which these attorneys
어느 배심원을
선발하고 거부할지
원고 측과 피고 측에서
선별하는 과정입니다
- will select or reject... - Hello?
여보세요?
You okay to talk?
대화 가능해요?
Uh... I'm okay to listen.
들을 순 있어
Annie just called in from Paris. Looks like Mossad's after Salma too.
애니가 파리에서
연락을 해왔어요
모사드도 샐마를
추적하고 있는 것 같아요
They sent Eyal Leven.
에이얼 라빈을 보냈어요
그래?
I don't think they'd send him on a fishing expedition,
정보조사차 라빈을
보내진 않았을 거예요
무언가 표적이
있기 때문이겠죠
so they must have a bead on something.
Are we hearing any chatter? What?
뭔가 소문은 없어?
네?
Are we hearing any-
들리는 소문...
chatter?
없냐고
아뇨, 지금 법정이에요?
No. Are you in the courtroom now?
응
The Israeli desk is checking on the deconfliction protocol.
이스라엘 부서에서는 충돌을
회피할 방법을 찾고 있고
애니가 입찰 경쟁에
뛰어들 경우를 대비해서
I went ahead and set up a line of credit
with the clearing bank in case Annie winds up in a bidding war.
어음 교환 협정 은행에
여신한도까지 준비시켜뒀어요
Okay. Well, just tell Annie no more buying bags.
알았어, 애니더러
가방 더 사지 말라고만 해둬
- Did I hear something banging? - No.
- 방금 총소리예요?
- 아냐
Bags. No more buying bags.
가방 말이야
가방 더 사지 말라고
9번 배심원!
Juror number nine!
Are we interrupting your phone conversation?
제가 통화를
방해했나요?
Uh... no.
아뇨
- I- - No, your honor.
아닙니다, 재판장님
We may proceed with voir dire.
예비 심문 선서를
진행하겠습니다
If I have your permission.
당신이 허락한다면?
Uh, yes, of course, your honor.
네, 물론이죠
재판장님
Voir dire away. Thank you, number nine.
진행하세요
고맙습니다
9번 배심원
춤 한 곡 추실래요?
WOULD YOU CARE TO DANCE?
I KNEW YOU'D COME AROUND.
당신이 올 줄 알았어요
당신은 미국인이죠?
YOU ARE AMERICAN, AREN'T YOU?
HOW'D YOU KNOW?
어떻게 아셨을까?
Lucky guess.
운이 좋았죠
제가...?
MAY I?
물론이죠
WITH PLEASURE.
I'm going to go freshen up.
잠깐 자리 좀 비울게요
So they have you seducing secretaries now?
비서를 유혹하라고
당신을 보낸 건가요?
And you with that tired old line about kismet.
그 지겨운 "운명"
얘기 하면서요
You're upset. I get that.
화났군요, 이해해요
You were so focused on following Salma,
샐마를 미행하는데
너무 집중한 나머지
you never realized you were being followed yourself.
당신이 미행당하는 걸
몰랐던 거죠
Listen, don't beat yourself up.
자책할 필요 없어요
내가 워낙
뛰어나기 때문이에요
- I'm really good at this. - So you like to tell me.
그 말을 하고 싶었군요
So how were you planning on turning her?
어떻게 전향시킬
계획이었어요?
It's the hardest thing we're tasked with.
우리가 다루는 임무 중에
가장 어려운 거죠
Make your pitch at the wrong time, in the wrong way,
it can all blow up in your face.
시간과 방법이
적절하지 않으면
전부 물거품이 되죠
How are you planning on getting her to spy for Mossad?
당신은 어떻게 모사드 쪽으로
만들 생각이었는데요?
- I'm not. - You're not?
- 그럴 생각 없어요
- 없다고요?
No. I'm gonna convince an impressionable young woman
네
나는 감수성 풍부한
저 젊은 아가씨가
to do a favor for her new lover.
새 애인의 부탁을
들어주게 할 거예요
It's a tactic tested in the field many times.
현장에서 여러 번
검증된 전략이죠
She will never know me as anyone but George Yiokas,
나를 조지 야코스로만
알게 될 거예요
키프로스 사업가죠
a businessman from Cyprus.
Don't get too cocky yet, neshama.
너무 자만하지 마세요
나도 아직 남아있는
카드가 있어요
I still have a few cards up my sleeve.
I'd keep them a little closer to my chest this time.
나도 이번엔 내 계획을
좀 더 감춰두도록 하죠
That was awkward.
이상한 일이에요
I just ran into someone from work.
직장 사람을
우연히 마주쳤어요
He asked me what I was doing here.
저보고 여기서
뭐하는 거냐고 묻더군요
- What did you tell him? - You did you say?
- 뭐라고 했어요?
- 뭐라고 대답했어요?
That you were an old friend from university
애니는 제 대학 때
친구라고 했어요
and that George here was a private art collector trying to get lucky.
조지는 개인 수집가인데
한 몫 잡으려 한다고 했고요
That sounds about right.
그 말이 딱인 거 같네요
This place is feeling a little tired. How about we get out of here?
여긴 조금 싫증나네요
그만 나가볼까요?
Perfect idea... Shall we?
훌륭한 생각이에요
가실까요?
이제야 좀 아늑하네요
Finally, some privacy.
It's getting late, George. Can we drop you somewhere?
시간이 많이 늦었네요
조지, 어디에 내려줄까요?
무슨 말씀이세요?
아직 밤은 길어요
What are you talking about? The night is still young.
I know this great little bar in the Marais.
마레에 멋진 바를 알아요
Why don't we just drive around a bit, okay?
일단 어디든
가보는 게 어때요?
어디로든 잠깐 가주세요
KEEP DRIVING FOR A WHILE, PLEASE.
네
Nothing like this ever happened to me before.
이런 일은 저에겐
전에 없던 일이에요
조금이라도 제게 관심을 보인
남자에게 만족해왔지만
I settle for the first guy who show me any interest,
and even he dumped me.
그 남자도 절 차버렸죠
And now, suddenly...
그런데 지금은
갑자기...
There is this stunning man and this so glamorous new friend
이렇게 멋진 남자와...
또 이렇게 매력적인
새 친구가...
fighting for my attention.
제 관심을 끌려
다투다니요
And I can only come up with one explanation.
이걸 설명할 길은
하나밖에 없어요
You want access to the embassy.
여러분은 대사관에
접근하고 싶은 거죠
- Embassy? - What are you talking about?
대사관이요?
- 엉뚱한 소리 말아요
- 무슨 소리예요?
애니는 CIA에서
일한다고 확신해요
I'm pretty sure Annie works with the CIA.
And if I have to guess, George here-
또 조지에 대해
짐작해보자면
당신 본명은 아니죠?
it's not your real name, is it? It's probably MI-6.
MI6일 수도 있겠군요
You seem too Jewish to be an actual Mossad officer.
모사드 요원으로 보기엔
지나치게 유대인 같아요
Too Jewish?
지나치게
유대인 같다고요?
I think you've had too much to drink.
술이 지나쳤던 거 같아요
- 제정신이 아닌 거 같아요
- 어쨌든...
- I think you've lost it. - Whatever.
Mahmoud Kanaan is coming to town tomorrow,
마흐무드 카나안은
내일 파리에 도착해요
and I know where.
저는 장소를 알아요
I've decided to auction off what I know
제가 아는 사실을
경매를 통해
for the highest bidder.
최고 입찰인에
알려주기로 했어요
저는 여기서 내려주세요
YOU CAN DROP ME OFF HERE, THANKS.
알겠습니다
If I'm right, I will be waiting for your offers.
제가 맞다면, 여러분의
제안을 기다리면 되겠죠
If I'm wrong, well...
제가 틀렸다면...
It was fun while it lasted.
그동안 즐거웠어요
I totally didn't see that coming.
이건 전혀 예상 못했네요
당신은요?
Did you?
What is it about you Americans
상대방이 최악으로
나오도록 하는
that brings out the worst in everyone you meet?
당신네 미국인들의
비결이 도대체 뭡니까?
어떤 상황이에요?
Where do we stand? I've got Salma on the other line.
지금 샐마와도
통화 중이에요
She says we have a deal at 50.
5만이면 거래할 수
있다고 하네요
50, 000 Euros. What happened to 30?
5만 유로요?
3만이라고 했잖아요?
3만은 30분 전이었죠
30 was half an hour ago, before Mossad made their final bid.
모사드에서
최종 제안하기 전이요
And you thought the pocketbook was expensive.
이래도 핸드백이
비쌌다고 생각해?
All right. Let me check with Joan.
알았어요
조안에게 확인해보죠
Why does it feel like we're bidding against ourselves?
왜 우리 자신에 맞서
입찰하는 기분이지?
We're supposed to be allies.
우린 그쪽 동맹이잖아
And there is no way Joan authorizes 50.
조안이 5만을
승인해줄 리도 없어
Not even to get a bead on Kanaan.
목표가 카나안이라
할지라도 말이야
We are confirmed up to 50, 000.
5만 승인합니다
성공시켜요, 애니
Make this happen, Annie.
Salma?
샐마?
- We got a deal. - Bon soir, Annie Walker.
거래해요
좋은 밤 되세요
애니 워커
Typical CIA, huh? Always taking shortcuts.
전형적인 CIA군요?
항상 지름길을 택하죠
She was supposed to meet me at the cafe at 11:00.
나랑 11시에 카페에서
만나기로 되어 있었어요
And me at the hotel at 11:30.
나하곤 11시 30분에
호텔에서 보기로 했는데요
She took both our offers?
양쪽 제안을
다 받아들인 거예요?
I'm beginning to like this girl more and more.
이 여자 점점 더
마음에 드는군요
Salma?
샐마?
거리 쪽을 맡을게요!
I'll cover the street!
Eyal!
에이얼!
Who sent you? What do you want?
누가 보냈지?
원하는 게 뭐야?
What do you want?
원하는 게 뭐냐고?
Que vois envoie? Que vois envoie?
손 잡아!
적어도 신고는
할 수 있었잖아요
Could have at least called it in. No. It will sort itself out.
아뇨, 알아서
해결될 거예요
Less trail we leave, the better.
우리 흔적을 적게
남길수록 좋아요
- So what now? - Now we part ways and go to ground.
그럼 이제 어쩌죠?
각자 추적을 피해
잠적해야죠
This is as good a place as any.
여느 장소처럼
파리도 잠적하기 좋죠
Since I'm not one for teary good-byes, let's leave it at au revoir.
눈물 섞인 작별은
내 타입은 아니니까
"안녕"이라고만
해둘게요
카나안은 어쩌고요?
What about Kanaan? What about Kanaan?
카나안이 뭐요?
Well, Salma obviously knew something for someone to want her dead.
샐마는 분명 샐마가 알고 있던
사실 때문에 죽은 거예요
And you're gonna find out how?
그걸 어떻게
알아내려고요?
By going back to her place? Good luck with that.
현장으로 돌아가 보려고?
잘해봐요
When I went through Salma's bag,
there was something missing from the day before.
예전과 비교해서 샐마의
가방에서 없어진 게 있었어요
전화번호가 적혀 있는
포스트잇이 없어졌어요
A post-it with a phone number on it.
It might have something to do with Kanaan.
카나안에 관한
내용일지도 몰라요
- If we put our heads together-
- I don't do the putting together of heads.
우리가 함께 계획을...
난 함께 계획해서
움직이지 않아요
- I work alone. - But I think-
- 난 혼자 움직여요
- 하지만 내 생각엔...
No buts. I can't be responsible for you.
하지만은 없어요
당신에 대해 책임질 수 없어요
We really gotta stop meeting like this.
이런 식으로 만나는 건
정말 그만둬야 해요
알았지?
셋에 하는 거야
Okay, on three, guys.
One, two, three.
하나, 둘, 셋
Happy Birthday!
생일 축하해요!
I hope we didn't wake you up in Topeka
토피카에서 너 깨운 게
아니었으면 좋겠다
디모인이던가?
or Des Moines
or wherever you are today.
네가 오늘 어디에
있든 말이야
We've got you on a new return flight at 1600 hours.
당신의 복귀 비행편을
16시로 해뒀어요
Auggie, is there a train arriving at Gare de Lyon at...
오기, 리옹 역에
도착하는 기차가...
2:17?
2시 17분에 있나요?
Yes. From Marseilles. Why?
네, 마르세유 발이에요
왜요?
I think I know where Kanaan's going to be.
카나안이 어디서
나타날지 알겠어요
And you've been working at the world bank for how long?
세계은행에서 일한지
얼마나 되셨죠?
11 years altogether,
총 11년입니다
Seven in development in the Balkans
7년은 발칸 지역에서 보냈고
지난 4년간 여기서 근무했어요
and the last four...
And in your capacity at the World Bank, have you come in contact with anyone-
세계은행에서의
당신의 지위로
다음과 같은 사람들과
접촉한 적...
I'm... sorry.
죄, 죄송해요
Would it be possible to request a recess?
휴회를 신청해도 될까요?
A recess.
휴회요?
It might be difficult for you, juror 9, as a banker,
당신에겐 힘든 일이겠어요
9번 배심원
은행 간부로서...
to fully grasp the concept of doing your civic duty.
시민의 의무를 다한다는
개념을 갖는 일이요
But I can assure you
하지만 확실히
말씀드리는데
that unlimited texting does not fall under its umbrella.
끊임없는 문자 메시지 전송은
결코 허용되지 않아요
Marshal, confiscate juror 9's phone, please.
집행관, 9번 배심원의
전화기를 압수해주세요
다른 소식은?
Any news? Joan's not getting back to me.
조안의 답신이 없어
I meant on Kanaan.
카나안 말이야
Annie thinks he might be arriving at the Gare de Lyon in 15 minutes.
애니 생각으론 카나안은
15분 안에
리옹역에 도착할 거야
Well, can she get there in time?
제시간에 갈 수 있대?
- Already in route. - Waiting for you
이미 이동 중이야
네 결정을 기다리고 있어
to make a decision.
Salma's dead. Mossad's already gone to ground,
샐마는 죽었고
모사드는 이미 잠적했고
애니가 당할 수도 있어
and Annie might be burned.
더구나 우린 카나안이
어떻게 생겼는지도 몰라
Plus, we have no idea what this guy even looks like.
따라서 카나안의 사진을
확보하는 일이 보다 가치있지
Which makes getting a photo of him all the more valuable.
Joan would bring her in. But you're not Joan.
조안이라면
불러들였을 거야
넌 조안이 아니잖아
여러분, 애니의 복귀 비행편을
늦춰놓도록 해요
Hey, guys, book Annie on a later return flight.
한 시간 내지 두 시간
더 필요합니다
- She needs another hour. Or two. - You got it, Auggie.
알았어요, 오기
Any idea how she's supposed to take a picture of someone
찾고 있는 사람이 누군지
아무도 모르는데
when no one knows who she's looking for?
어떻게 사진을
찍을 수 있을까?
찍었어요?
Did you get it?
Got it.
물론이죠
That's a good picture. The frame... The mise-en-scene...
잘 찍었네요
구성이나... 배경도
계속해봐요
Go on.
Yeah? What do you want? You want an award?
원하는 게 뭔데요?
상장이라도?
No. I'm not a prideful person.
아뇨, 난 그렇게
교만하지 않아요
그래도 칭찬 받는 건
언제나 기쁘죠
It's always nice, a few accolades, though.
Oh, you want accolades.
원하는 게
칭찬이군요
All right.
좋아요
Here's some for you.
당신에게 바치는 거예요
You have a little game, Annie Walker.
당신은 제법이에요
애니 워커
당신이 해온 일을 보면
I've seen a few in action.
So many have trouble improvising,
예상치 못한 문제들이
생겨날 때마다
but you... you have some gears to shift into.
당신에겐 잘 헤쳐나갈
방법이 있었죠
And you have, uh, great interpersonal skills.
그리고 당신에겐...
대인관계에 대한
훌륭한 기술이 있어요
See, I agree, but my family doesn't think so.
나도 그렇게 생각하지만
가족들은 동의하지 않아요
Family?
가족이요?
My sister. She thinks I'm lying
우리 언니요
언니는 내가 거짓말쟁이에
비밀스러운 외톨이라고 생각해요
and secretive and isolated.
She also thinks I'm in Topeka.
지금은 내가 토피카에
있다고 알고 있죠
- And you're close with her. - Very.
언니와 가까운 사이군요
무척이요
- But she doesn't know... - Anything.
- 하지만 언니는 전혀...
- 전혀 몰라요
That's how the agency likes it.
CIA란 게 그렇죠
And you?
당신은요?
I used to tell my wife everything.
아내에게 모든 걸
얘기하곤 했어요
You did? That's how Mossad likes it.
그래요?
모사드는 그래요
They think it helps
모사드에선
도움이 된다고 생각해요
to have someone at home who knows where you are,
집안에 누군가가 정체와
하는 일을 알고 있다면요
what you're doing.
Helps tether you to something concrete.
당신을 붙잡아줄
단단한 무언가가 되는 거죠
Of course, then they get to worry about you instead of living blissfully in ignorance...
물론 모르는 채 행복하게 사는
대신 당신을 걱정하게 되죠
So in a way, it's kind of selfish to tell them.
그런 점에서 가족들에게
말하는 건 이기적이에요
Or at least, that's what my wife said when she was leaving me.
아니면 적어도 아내가
날 떠날 때 했던 말이긴 해요
Are you gonna tell me how you found me at that train station?
날 어떻게 역에서 찾았는지
이야기해줄 거예요?
Or was it just a lucky guess?
그냥 운이 좋았던 거예요?
Just...
그냥...
Good trade craft.
스파이 기술이었어요
- Mm. - I don't believe in luck. Really?
난 운을 믿지 않아요
그래요?
So what time's your flight?
비행편은 언제예요?
한 잔 더할 시간 있나요?
You up for one more or, uh,
you gotta call it quits?
그만 가야 하나요?
I think I have time for one more.
시간 될 거 같아요
But only if you come clean about the train station.
기차역에 어떻게
나왔는지 말해주면요
Deal. Oh, hey, hold on a second.
좋아요
아, 잠시만요
당신 여기...
You have a little, uh...
Little schmutz on your collar here.
칼라에 얼룩이 묻었네요
Merci. No problem.
고마워요
별말씀을
Oh, and have them make mine a little dirtier next time.
아, 그리고 내 다음 잔은
좀 더 독한 걸로 주문해줘요
The man that was sitting right here-
여기 앉아 있던
남자 말인데요
택시!
Taxi...! Alright, alright.
Talk to me.
말해요
- My location? - 49 and 03 degrees north,
제 위치는요?
북위 49도 03분
동경 3도 56분이에요
3 and 56 east, just outside Epernay.
에페르네 교외예요
Now, hang tight. The cavalry's on the way.
그대로 있어요
부대가 출동 중이에요
Yeah. I need more details than that.
그보다 더 자세한
설명이 필요한데요
15, 20 minutes tops.
15분, 길어도 20분이요
훈련소에서 가르쳐준
교육과정 기억나요?
Remember that course they taught at the farm?
How if you're captured... You've got an hour or so to escape?
잡혔을 때
한 시간 안에
탈출해야 한다는 거요?
And after that, the odds of survival go to...
한 시간 이후의
생존 확률은
Next to nothing.
없는 것과
다름 없다던...
Yeah.
네
에이얼을 납치한 지
한 시간이 됐어요
They've had Eyal for over an hour now.
Annie... you're what- one against four, five?
애니, 어떻게 하려고요?
혼자서 넷? 다섯을?
They have a video camera, Auggie.
카메라를 저들이
가지고 있어요, 오기
And you're not even armed.
당신은 심지어
비무장 상태잖아요
He doesn't have anyone looking out for him but me.
에이얼을 도울 사람은
나밖에 없어요
Okay.
알았어요
함께 해결해봐요
Let's work the problem.
Tell me everything you see.
보이는 모든 걸 말해줘요
You okay? Some explosion. You cleared the room.
괜찮아요?
굉장한 폭발이었어요
방을 비우게 하다니
여길 벗어날 방법도 있겠죠?
I assume you have a way out of here?
Yeah. There's a truck outside.
네, 밖에 트럭이 있어요
The keys are in the ignition. I checked.
키도 꽂혀 있고요
확인했어요
Any chance you've been issued a gun yet?
아직 총을 꺼낼 때
안 됐어요?
- Not yet. - Yeah. This is a good plan.
아직 아니에요
네, 훌륭한 계획이군요
가요
Let's go!
What do you think?
어떻게 생각해요?
Ha ha ha. They suit you.
잘 어울려요
밴을 폭파시키기 전에
You could have pulled out my shoes,
내 신발을 꺼내둘 수도
있었잖아요
out of that van, before you blew it up.
Well, maybe if you were more interested in
watching your back instead of stealing my memory card...
당신이 내 메모리 카드를
훔치는 것보다
등 뒤를 조심하는데
더 신경 썼더라면...
Yeah. Yeah, well, that was painfully easy, wasn't it?
그건 정말이지 쉬웠어요
안 그래요?
The schmutz on the collar routine.
칼라에 묻은 얼룩
수법이라니
당신이 유대어로 말했을 때
경계해야 했었는데
A red flag should have gone up when you brought out the yiddish.
Where is my memory card, by the way?
그건 그렇고
내 메모리 카드 어딨어요?
You didn't. The photo of Kanaan!
설마...
카나안 사진이요!
Something for the higher-ups to figure out.
높으신 양반들이
알아서 하겠죠
- That's me. - Right.
- 제 비행편이에요
- 그렇군요
농장으로 당신 쫓아갈 때
택시 영수증을 깜빡했어요
I forgot to get a receipt from the cab
when I went to the farmhouse.
Well, we can take care of that. Hold on a second.
그건 해결할 수 있죠
잠시만요
What are you doing? I don't know about Langley,
뭐하는 거예요?
랭리는 어떨지 모르겠는데
but these work fine for Mossad.
모사드에선
이 방법이 잘 먹혀요
So how much did it cost you?
얼마 들었어요?
500 euro.
500 유로요
500?
오백?
Wow. You got totally ripped off.
바가지 제대로 썼군요
You would have done the same thing for me.
당신도 날 위해
똑같이 해줬을 거예요
At those prices... Not a chance.
그 정도 가격이라면...
어림도 없어요
비행기 놓치겠어요
You don't want to miss your plane.
Right.
네
HAPPY BIRTHDAY. E
생일 축하해요 - E
배심원 석에
남아계신 분들은
If you're still sitting in the box, then you will be serving on this jury.
배심원으로 일하게 됩니다
이번 재판은 두 가지 중
하나의 방법으로 진행됩니다
Now, I can see this trial going one of two ways.
It could carry on for an extended period of time,
시간을 연장해서
진행되거나
or we could be out of here in three weeks.
3주 내로
끝마치게 됩니다
다들 편안히 생각하세요
So let's get comfortable.
Yes, number 9.
네, 9번 배심원?
Your honor,
재판장님
I know this might sound self-aggrandizing,
저 자신을 과대평가한다고
생각하실지도 모르지만
but I cannot sit on a three-week trial.
3주 동안이나 재판에
묶여 있을 수 없어요
직장에서 저를
필요로 해요
My job needs me. You're right, number 9.
당신 말이 맞아요
9번 배심원
I do hear the sound of your own horn tooting.
당신의 자화자찬 소리가
귀에 거슬리는군요
Sit down.
앉으세요
Now, it is useful
이제, 재판의 각 단계를
for you to know what the various parts of the trial are.
여러분이 알고 있으면
유용합니다
전화기를
빌릴 수 있을까요?
Can I borrow your phone, please?
재판 기간 내내
여러분이 알고 계셔야 할
... that you may be aware throughout the trial
각 절차의 단계와...
what stage of the proceedings is in..
20달러 드릴게요
- I will pay you $20. - progress and what comes next.
...다음 단계에 대한 겁니다
The trial starts with opening statements by the lawyers,
재판은 변호사들의
개시 연설로 시작합니다
and then they will state the nature
그리고 각 측이 주장하는
자연적, 법적 권리의 본질에
대해서 진술하게 됩니다
of their factual and legal claims.
Opening statements are not proof of evidence...
개시 연설은
증거가 아니며
단순히 권리에...
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
고마워요
별말씀을
Now, so that you will be aware
이제, 여러분이 듣게 되는
법적 권리의 증거를 알게...
as you hear the evidence of the legal claim-
Excuse me.
실례합니다
Thank you.
고마워요
Juror number 9.
9번 배심원?
You have been excused from serving on this jury.
배심원의 의무를
다하지 못한다는
당신의 양해를
받아들입니다
The court would like to thank you for your service to your community.
본 법정은 사회에 대한
당신의 봉사에 감사드립니다
Thank you, your honor.
감사합니다, 재판장님
Can I have my phone, please?
전화기 돌려주시겠어요?
Excuse me. Excuse me.
실례합니다
실례해요
Mossad just cabled this over.
모사드에서 보내줬어요
They tell me it's a nice shot.
잘 찍은 사진이라고
들었어요
Well, at least we know he's not a figment of our imagination.
적어도 우리 상상의 산물이
아니란 건 알게 됐네
It's not easy, is it...
쉽지 않지?
Making decisions that affect your friends' safety?
친구의 안전과 관계된
결정을 내리는 일 말이야
No, it's not.
네, 쉽지 않아요
Got news for you.
알려줄 게 있어
Doesn't get any easier.
앞으로도 쉬워지지 않아
들어오는 소릴
들은 것 같았어
I thought I heard you come in.
Oh. I didn't want to wake you.
깨울 생각 없었는데
Thank you so much for the message that you sent.
메시지 보내줘서
정말 고마워
It came at the perfect time.
정말 때마침 온
메시지였어
You will never know how much that meant to me.
얼마나 기뻤는지
언니는 모를 거야
So how was Topeka?
토피카는 어땠어?
Actually...
사실은...
I didn't go to Topeka. I went to Paris.
토피카에 갔던 게 아니야
파리에 갔었어
Paris? As in Paris, Paris?
파리?
파리라면 그 파리?
Oui.
맞아
How did that happen?
어쩌다가?
It was a last-minute thing at work.
마지막에 그렇게 결정됐어
Oh-my-freaking-God!
세상에 맙소사!
That's exactly what I said when they told me- Just like that.
나도 얘기 듣고
똑같은 반응이었어
You little scamp.
날라리 같은 계집애
I'm sorry I didn't tell you.
말 안 해서 미안해
I feel horrible about it.
정말 미안하게 생각해
- It's okay. - No.
괜찮아
아니야, 안 괜찮아
It's not okay. It's not.
저게 내가 생각하는 거야?
Is that what I think it is?
맞아
Yeah.
I wanted to spoil myself for my birthday.
내 생일이니까
한번 질렀지
Good for you.
잘했어
You deserve it.
받을만하지
이게 최신 유행은
아니겠지만
Now, this might not be high fashion...
But it is homemade.
그래도 집에서 만든 거야
Happy Birthday.
생일 축하해
피드백
whemie@gmail.com
팎읔襟俚캥莉
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
뻑短속흙